[{"answer": "I'm sorry, my friend.  My old Dad used to say 'when you can't change a situation, laugh at it.' Nothing ridicules a thing like laughing at it", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " The only girlish thing you have lost", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Okay. What do we do instead, write each other lurid love letters", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "And I'm a working man! We're a regular workin", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "We can see each other, we can even have dinner... but respectably, in my house with my mother's picture on the mantel and my sister helping me broil a big steak for three", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " I don't! That's how I'm able to keep it!", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Speakin' of feeling good, where's that bottle you said you had in your desk...  Oops!  Usually I can keep my mouth shut", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Then I'm free to go...", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Of course not! Am I acting as if... something's wrong", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Dirty night", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " We have twelve vacancies. Twelve cabins, twelve vacancies.  They moved away the highway", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " I'll be in the office if you want anything... just tap on the wall", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Why don't you go away", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "No, not like me", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Yes, and just one time can be enough.  Thank you", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Let's all talk about my friend", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "my friend, Private Investigator.  Where is she, my friend", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " In the past two days I've been to so many motels, my eyes are bleary with neon. This is the first one that looked like it was hiding from the world at large", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Sit down. I don't want to trouble you, just want to ask..", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Hundreds! Which one is your pet", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I feel better when you feel better", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "No Arbogast. No my friend. And only the old lady at home...  A sick old lady unable to answer the door... or unwilling", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Maybe he got some definite lead. Maybe he went right on..", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "In a hurry", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " Yes. I think he would have", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " Now. Your sister is missing how long", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "How'd you and this detective come to trace her to that place", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend found them dead together.  In bed", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " Maybe you saw my friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " No! I will not hide in the fruit cellar!  Think I'm fruity, huh?  I'm staying right here!  This is my room and no one will drag me out of it... least of all my big bold son", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " Just for a few days...  In that dank fruit cellar? No!  You hid me there once, boy, and you won't do it again! Not ever again!  Now get out!  I told you to get out, boy!  my friend! What do you think you're going to do? Don't you touch me! Don't! my friend!  All right, son, put me down and I'll go. I'll go on my own two feet. I can go on my own two feet, can't I", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " You look frightened. Have I been saying something frightening", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I've been talking about your mother... about your motel. How are you going to do it", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Yes... and no", "docId": "psycho_revised.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "A psychiatrist doesn't lay the groundwork .. he merely tries to explain it", "qsentId": 38}]